Guide to the Wesley H. Greene Papers 1900-1996
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Film Distribution
  - Subseries 2: Movie Posters and Oversize Publicity Material
    - Desire under the Elms, circa 1958 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Doña Barbara, circa 1943 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Duke of West Point, circa 1938 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Elephant Boy, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Flushing Meadow Improvement, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Der Klösterjäger, circa 1935 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence of Arabia, circa 1962 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Life of Riley, circa 1930s (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Little Flower: St. Therese of Lisieux, circa 1930s (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Der Maulkorb, circa 1938 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Les Misérables, circa 1935 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Motion Picture Exhibitor, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Mystic Mountain, circa 1936 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Portrait of a Woman, circa 1942 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Rio Escondido, circa 1948 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Ski Chase, circa 1936 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Southern Star, circa 1969 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Tant Qu'on à la Santé, circa 1966 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Trans-World Films, catalog layout, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - La Traversée de Paris, circa 1956 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - UniFrance Film, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Am-As, Amazing Monsieur Fabre, circa 1952 Angelika, circa 1954 Associated British-Pathe Limited, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Aventura en las Islas Cies, circa 1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Bi-Bl, Bicycle Thief, circa 1948 Bittersweet, circa 1933 Blithe Spirit, circa 1940s (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Ca-Cr, Caged Women, circa 1953 Chantaje, circa 1960s Crisis, circa 1960s (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Daughters of Destiny, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Deutscher Film Export, circa 1960s (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Diary of Sueko, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Emil und die Detektive, circa 1931 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Fa-Fi, Father's Dilemma, circa 1950 Females at Play, undated Fire under Her Skin, circa 1954 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Forza del Destino, circa 1949 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - F.P.1, circa 1933 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - The Gang, circa 1930s (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - ...and God Created Woman, circa 1956 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Good Companions, circa 1933 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Good Times, circa 1967 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - The Great Mr. Handel, circa 1942 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Harvest, circa 1936 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Heritage, circa 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Der Herrscher, circa 1937 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - El Hombre de Papel, circa 1963 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - House Beautiful, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - I Was a Spy, circa 1933 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Imperial Enterprise, Inc., 1954 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Isola Bella, circa 1961 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Janitizio, circa 1935 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Kefauver, Estes, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Das Letzte Kapitel, circa 1960s (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Lo-Ma, Love is My Profession, circa 1958 Maxime, circa 1958 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Les Misérables, circa 1935 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Missouri Traveler, circa 1958 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - My Seven Little Sins, circa 1954 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Nazarin, circa 1959 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - No Greater Love, circa 1932 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - No Sun in Venice, circa 1957 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - O-Ro, Orchids to Angelo, circa 1950s Le Plaisir, circa 1952 The Proud and the Beautiful, circa 1953 The Quiet One, circa 1948 Rigoletto, circa 1946 Round the Bend, undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Rubens, circa 1949 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Samurai, circa 1956 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Scarlet Week, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Seine Tochter ist der Peter, circa 1936 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Seven Deadly Sins, undated (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - So-St, Song of Freedom, circa 1936 Stella, circa 1950s (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - That They May Live, circa 1939 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - This Strange Passion, undated (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Titan: The Story of Michelangelo, circa 1950 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - To the Victor, circa 1948 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Transatlantic Tunnel, circa 1935 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Un-, Under the Paris Sky, circa 1951 Union Film Distributors, Inc., circa 1950s-1960s (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Una Vida Por Otra, circa 1932 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Virtuous Bigamist, circa 1956 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - W-, When Comedy Was King, 1966 The Witch, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Zwei Herzen im ¾ Takt, circa 1930 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - A-O, Angele, circa 1939 Club de Femmes, circa 1936 Madame Butterfly, circa 1950s Naked Eye, circa 1956 The Night Heaven Fell, circa 1958 Orpheus, circa 1950 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Ra-Ro, Rasputin, 1939 The Rebel, circa 1930s Rome Express, circa 1932 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Round Trip, circa 1938 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - S-U, Ski Chase, circa 1936 UFA Films, circa 1930s (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Adventures of Chico, circa 1938 (Box FOLDER 1)
    - Maria Candelaria, circa 1944 (Box FOLDER 1)
    - Victoria the Great, circa 1937 (Box FOLDER 1)
    - Unidentified German film, circa 1930s (Box FOLDER 2)
- Series II: Chicago Film Council
  - Membership and attendance, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Film Council of America, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 2-5)
  - Spring Film Festival, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Films of the World Festival, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 7-10)
  - Films of the World Festival, pamphlets, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 11-12)
  - Films of the World Festival, press releases, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Films of the World Festival, screening committee, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Premiere and preview screenings, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Series III: University of Chicago
  - University Film Society, programs, circa 1932 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - "Foreign Films at International House," reprint, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - International House and Renaissance Society film series, programs, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 6-11)
  - International House and Renaissance Society film series, programs, 1935-1939 (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
  - International House and Renaissance Society film series, programs, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 1-5)
  - Notes and address cards, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - International House newsletter, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Committee to Preserve the Ferguson Fund for Sculpture
  - Correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box 32, Folder 8-10)
  - Clippings, publications and press releases, 1957-1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Wesley Greene vs. the Art Institute of Chicago and the Northern Trust Company, complaints and petitions, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Financial records, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - General, 1946-1958 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
- Series V: Personal
  - Date books, 1900, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Randolph-Macon College Yellow Jacket, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Allegheny College Kaldron, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - University High School Correlator, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Luther Greene, correspondence and biographical material, 1944- 1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Wesley H. Greene, biographical statements, circa 1948-1968 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Home renovation materials, circa 1961 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Henry Kakehashi, draft, circa 1960s (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Political clippings and publicity material, circa 1950s-1980s (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
  - Travel material, circa 1930s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
  - Periodicals, clippings and publicity material, circa 1950s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 3-7)
  - Periodicals, clippings and publicity material, circa 1950s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - Unidentified files, circa 1940s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 4-10)
  - Unidentified files, circa 1940s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 1-7)
- Series VI: Restricted
  - International Film Bureau, financial records, 1967-1996 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
  - Personal medical and financial records, 1946-1996 (Box 38, Folder 4)